A Guide to the Edwin Fisher Conger Papers, 1900-1979
Virginia Historical Society
- Edwin F. Conger Personal Files 1916-1967
  - Personal and Family Papers. 1916-1967
    - E. F. Conger: General Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 2:91)
    - E. F. Conger: General Correspondence, William H. Clark, 1965 (Box 2:92)
    - E. F. Conger: General Correspondence, William H. Clark, 1966 (Box 2:93)
    - E. F. Conger: General Correspondence, William H. Clark, 1967 (Box 2:94)
    - E. F. Conger: Higgs/Redmond case file, 1963-1964 (Box 2:95)
    - E. F. Conger: Homestead, Hot Springs, Va., visit, 1946 (Box 2:96)
    - E. F. Conger: Horse Point Estates, Middlesex County, Va., purchase, 1954 (Box 2:97)
    - E. F. Conger: Horse Point property, plat, undated (see oversize) (Box 2:98)
    - E. F. Conger: Horse Point Estates file, 1965 (Box 2:99)
    - E. F. Conger: Horse Point Estates file, 1966 (Box 2:100)
    - E. F. Conger: Horse Point Estates file, 1967 (Box 2:101)
    - E. F. Conger: Houghton Fortnightly Club (Florida), 1950-1952 (Box 3:102)
    - E. F. Conger: Insurance file, 1965 (Box 3:103)
    - E. F. Conger: Insurance file, 1966 (Box 3:104)
    - E. F. Conger: Insurance file, 1967 (Box 3:105)
    - E. F. Conger: John W. Johnson (caretaker), purchase of house and lot on Bagby Street, Staunton, Va., 1962-1966 (Box 3:106)
    - E. F. Conger: LeBow, Vivion Conger (daughter), Correspondence file, 1941-1966 (Box 3:107)
    - E. F. Conger: LeBow, Vivion Conger, Trust file, 1965-1967 (Box 3:108)
    - E. F. Conger: Mary Baldwin College Science Center Advisory Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 3:109)
    - E. F. Conger: Meador, Bruce Bennett, recommendation to N.C State School of Forestry, 1966 (Box 3:110)
    - E. F. Conger: Meteor file (yacht) (Box 3:111)
    - E. F. Conger: Nassau Trip, 1939 (Box 3:112)
    - E. F. Conger: New Hampshire trip, 1940 (Box 3:113)
    - E. F. Conger: Ormond Beach, Fla., trip, 1946 (Box 3:114)
    - E. F. Conger: Palm Beach, Fla., trip, 1943 (Box 3:115)
    - E. F. Conger: Petersham, Mass., file (postcards), 1949 (Box 3:116)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Bill on Furlough, 1941, 1941 (Box 3:117)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Booten Farm, Orange County, Va. (Box 3:118)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Coconut Grove, Miami, Fla., undated (Box 3:119)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family, 1947 (Box 3:120)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family (miscellaneous) (Box 3:121)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family (miscellaneous) (Box 3:122)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family (miscellaneous) (Box 3:123)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family (miscellaneous) (Box 3:124)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family (miscellaneous-Staunton, Va.) (Box 3:125)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Conger Family and Associates (Box 3:126)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Eager family (grandchildren), 1952-1953 (Box 3:127)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Eager, Howard Lloyd and Edwin F., 1952 (Box 3:128)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Eager, Howard Lloyd (Box 3:129)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Family vacation, 1941 (Box 3:130)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Florida Trip, 1949 (Box 3:131)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Florida vacation, 1950 (Box 3:132)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Grand, Dorothea Conger and Brooks D., 1948 (Box 3:133)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Jarman, Dr. L. Wilson, Winter Park, Fla., 1952 (Box 3:134)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Key Biscayne, Fla., 1953 (Box 3:135)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Long Island, N.Y.; N.J.; Natural Bridge, Va. (Box 3:136)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Montgomery/Jennings wedding, 1956? (Box 3:137)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Orlando, Fla., 1940 (Box 3:138)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Ormond, Fla., 1948 (Box 3:139)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Point Pleasant, N. J., 1937 (Box 3:140)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Point Pleasant, N.J., Hurricane Damage, 1939 (Box 3:141)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Eddy Rockefeller Florida Trip, undated (Box 3:142)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Santa Elena Cruise, 1938 (Box 3:143)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Staunton, Va., residence, 1949 (Box 3:144)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Summer, 1940 (Box 3:145)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Summer, 1941 (Box 3:146)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Travel Photos, 1916 (Box 3:147)
    - E. F. Conger: Photographs, Western College for Women (Oxford, Ohio), 1941 (Box 3:148)
    - E. F. Conger: Summer Trip, 1951 (Box 3:149)
    - E. F. Conger: Sverker, Dorothea Conger Eager Grand (daughter), Divorce and Remarriage, 1947-1948 (Box 3:150)
    - E. F. Conger: Sverker, Dorothea Conger Eager Grand, Trust file, 1966-1968 (Box 3:151)
    - E. F. Conger: Tax file, 1927 (Box 3:152)
    - E. F. Conger: Tax file, 1931 (Box 3:153)
    - E. F. Conger: Tax, Trusts, and Estate Planning file, 1965 (Box 3:154)
    - E. F. Conger: Tax file, 1966 (Box 3:155)
    - E. F. Conger: Tax and Estate Planning file, 1967 (Box 3:156)
    - E. F. Conger: Travel file, 1948 (Box 3:157)
    - E. F. Conger: U.S. Interstate Route 64 file (with map of Charlottesville, Va.) (see oversize) (Box 3:158)
    - E. F. Conger: Winter Park, Fla., trip, ca. 1948 (Box 3:159)
    - E. F. Conger: Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation, Inc., 1964 (Box 3:160)
    - E. F. Conger: Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 3:161)
    - E. F. Conger: Y.M.C.A., Staunton, Va., 1966 (Box 3:162)
- Conger Family Personal Files. 1929-1979
  This series contains just a few files of the wife and second daughter of Edwin F. Conger. Dorothea Lloyd (Tatum) Conger (1893-1961) worked most of her years of marriage as treasurer of companies her husband acquired and operated. Some of her letters to her two daughters are found in Conger's correspondence files. The file of genealogical materials, primarily focused on her Tatum family ancestors and relations, is the largest grouping of materials of or about Mrs. Conger. A small amount of financial material relating to Vivion Randolph (Conger) LeBow (1923-2006), who left her father's papers to the Virginia Historical Society, completes the collection.
  - Dorothea Lloyd (Tatum) Conger: Tax file, 1929 (Box-folder 3:163)
  - Dorothea Lloyd (Tatum) Conger: Genealogical materials file (primarily Randolph and Tatum families) (see also oversize) (Box-folder 3:164)
  - Vivion (Conger) LeBow: Financial file, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 3:165)